# JONEER

# **ABOUT ME**

I am a veteran, technologist, lifelong learner & open source enthusiast. My focus is on taking my software development skills to the next level. I am a chronic open-source contributor and have a lot of experience with distributed collaboration. I am a team player and clear communicator who focuses on team success. Currently, I am working on mastering the MEAN stack.

# **EXPERIENCE**

### **NEWTON**

### MOBILE APPLICATION DEVELOPER

Develops, maintains, and deploys decentralized applications to meet the needs of decentralized finance customers and crypto users. Tech: React Native, Node.js, CSS, Git, JavaScript, TypeScript, XCode, VSCode, Android Studio. Jun 2022 - Present

### **JAMBB**

### WEB DEVELOPER

Architects, maintains, and deploys smart contracts and decentralized applications to meet the needs of hundreds of thousands of fans. Tech: Docker, Node.js, Cadence, Solidity, Hardhat, IPFS, Nuxt, Vue, Tailwind, Git, TypeScript. Jan 2022 - Jun 2022

### **FARM BUREAU BANK**

### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Responsible for the development and maintenance of internal and external web applications and tools. Writes, tests, develops and implements custom programs to streamline financial institution workflows. Tech: jQuery, HTML, CSS, MySQL. May 2019 - Jan 2022

## **CNF TECHNOLOGIES**

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (CONTRACT)

Responsible for developing and maintaining the full stack of a website utilized by the U.S. Air Force to maintain and track data on cryptographic products. Tech: ASP.NET, jQuery, HTML, CSS, MySQL DataTables, Bootbox, Font Awesome & Bootstrap. Mar - Dec 2018

# CONTACT

kevinjones.engineer github.com/joneskj55 linkedin.com/in/joneskj55 joneskj55@gmail.com

# **EDUCATION**

### BELLEVUE UNIVERSITY

2020 - 2022 | BS Web Development

### CODEUP

2016 - 2017 | Full-Stack Web Development Certificate

# **SKILLS**

JavaScript Git
TypeScript CSS
Node.js HTML
Vue.js Express
React MongoDB
Angular Tailwind